Apple number seven there will be some
other ones I think there are a lot of
realms where we have delegated the
authority to our government for obvious
reasons because when you have a
corporation against a consumer and like
is this going to cause cancer is it's
going to destroy our planet we would
like to know that there's someone
standing up for us especially in a world
where the internet didn't exist and we
needed to believe the government had
more knowledge than we did but now that
the internet does exist and governments
have been shown to be just as corrupt as
corporations it's hard for me to trust
them fully even though I'm glad that
they exist to some degree so be able to
take that power back I don't think
necessarily means lobbying and getting
getting the power back but just starting
where we are and say it okay
well if I can't trust you to make sure
that my soil and water and air are clean
then I'm going to trust us to do that
and I think part of where that happens
is in testing so to test the soil all
around or be live and that involves
community labs which is maybe another
whole other Apple because it's something
that doesn't happen on day one it's when
there's millions of people involved not
one person involved and so community
labs but in the meantime you can have if
it costs instead of hundreds of dollars
to get your stuff tested costs $10 or $1
and you're able to start community labs
in larger cities and test the water and
the I don't actually know how you test
the air but test the soil and have
temperature I mean now I'm in Canada so
I'm not in America but with Trump's
taking down all the environmental
information off the government EP I
think it is in front Protection Agency
website that's ridiculous
that should never be allowed to happen
because it should be in the hands of the
people not the government so we should
have all the information that would have
been available there available on backup
so it's you can't
take it down because we happen I think
they do actually I think they knew that
was going to kind of happen and so
information what that was on their
husband saved but anyway that's probably
off all the way but be able to own our
own information to be able to map the
help of soil and water all over the
world because we do it so I could to
take it from my backyard and if my
neighbors agreed I could take it from
their backyards
I could take it from by the road and by
I mean but when it's hundreds of dollars
to test it then that's going to be
really impossible for me to afford that
but if there were ten thousand people
who did that through okay Cooper and we
were able to get a deal so it was you
know I don't know hundred thousand
dollars so it was ten dollars per sample
that would be more feasible and each
person puts in ten ten dollars and gets
our soil and we plot it that's yes one
of the ideas is we take back the EPA and
that's that's like a small section of
EPA that's just like soil and water
testing but where we have community labs
and we're able to do our own testing and
especially if it's ten thousand people
doing it and ten thousand people say in
their soil sample there's going to be
less likely to be corruption or the
ability to false have false data if
you're all in the same lab that's
another another issue probably would be
but as we are able to send in samples
all over the world to different
organizations and follow it I think we
have will just have way more information
which gold make us more powerful